dragonadopters.com 2013-05-02

# Dragonadopters Home

Your privacy is critically important to us. At Dragonadopters we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it.
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.  

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our support team.  
It is our policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our website.

**Website Visitors**  
Like most website operators, Dragonadopters collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Our purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how you the visitors use this website. From time to time, Dragonadopters may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

Dragonadopters also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. We do not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

**Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information**  
Certain visitors to the Dragonadopters website choose to interact with Dragonadopters in ways that require us to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that we gather depends on the nature of the interaction. Those who engage in transactions with Dragonadopters – by purchasing coins or other services, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, Dragonadopters collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with Dragonadopters. Dragonadopters does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

**Aggregated Statistics**  
Dragonadopters may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. However, Dragonadopters does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**  
Dragonadopters discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Dragonadopters behalf or to provide services available at the Dragoadopters’ website, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Dragonadopters’ websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Dragonadopters will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Dragonadopters discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Dragonadopters believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Dragonadopters, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user and have supplied your email address, Dragonadopters may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with Dragonadopters and our products. We primarily use our news and forums to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Dragonadopters takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Dragonadopters uses cookies to help Dragonadopters identify and track visitors, their usage of the Dragonadopters website, and their website access preferences. Visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using the Dragonadopters website, with the drawback that certain features of the website may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

**Ads**  
Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Dragonadopters and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.  
Dragonadopters does not support or is responsible for any advertisement contents.

**Privacy Policy Changes**  
Although most changes are likely to be minor, Dragonadopters may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Dragonadopters’ sole discretion. Dragonadopters encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

**Change log:**  
June 29, 2010: First Version
